[{"answer": "Just because a marriage doesn't last forever doesn't mean it's a failure.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Married twice, divorced twice, what the hell does he know about it?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Phaedra Parks.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Do you have a secret admirer, Piers?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Kandi Burruss.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "So who has time for romance?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "Jump right into it.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Donny Deutsch, you've been married and divorced twice, what do you think gives you the possible right to now put yourself up there as Mr. Love Guru expert to the nation's women?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Are you reformed character?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "And the other ones are 3 and 7.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "One of them is 24 years old?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I think that it's a combination of age, it's a combination of mistakes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "You just changed or?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I don't think men by nature are what I call romantic.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Are men romantic really?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "She loves football.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Does she like football?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Here's why.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I'm flawed but I think very funny.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Are you a fine human being?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "The flaws --", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "What are the flaws?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do we have an hour?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Maybe because where I was in my career, I think the third time will be the charm for me.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "EUTSCH: I think so.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "You think you will get remarried again?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Third time?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "You've been married twice, right?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "I was married to two great women.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "When you look back on it, what have you learned?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "EUTSCH: I must say (INAUDIBLE), but I do think like in anything, in a business relationship, in a friendship, in any type of a partnership, it's not unconditional.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "And you ask yourselves together, should we renew this contract, this business arrangement we have?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you believe that (INAUDIBLE) change their spots?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Are women taking this seriously so far?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "-- are believing you're some sort of love guru?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Yes, it's like, just get over right.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "And you refer to things as what?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I can't really.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "You can't say that with a straight face, can you?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "As a powerful ad man, you know, one of the top executives in New York and you've seen how America has gone through a very tough period.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Everybody's got something, right?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I think what I would do, and I know this is not going to be a popular answer.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What would you do to get America back on its feet?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Well, if you look at the history of the world there needs to be a check and balance.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "But isn't the answer really to do business with them?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "She's unelectable.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "What is your assessment of her as a potential challenger to the White House?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Is every brand rescuable?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "She's waiting to happen.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "I mean, it's Lindsay Lohan right now, if you were able to rebrand her, you could rescue her?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Somebody that commits a horrible act to children or somebody that murders, or someone -- we even saw Michael Vick, you know, who did an almost horrific, horrific thing, and what he did with these dogs.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Who is not rescuable?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Power, no question.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Which has been the biggest aphrodisiac to women?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How appealing do you think you are to women?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Rich, handsome, powerful and a big house.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "And I want any control -- I want to play back how many times you said rich, handsome, powerful -- what were the other ones?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Before we go any further, ladies, I want you to respond immediately to Donny's claims -- his two claims, really.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Hello, great, how are you?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I would have to say I do like a bit of a bad boy.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What is your instant reaction?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do you know now?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Is he the kind of guy a woman would go to for genuine advice about her difficulties with a man?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I would think so.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I'm not sure.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I didn't say about to.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Would you look at him now, with this cheeky grin, the twinkle in the eye, and think I reckon he's about to settle down seriously?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Ladies, we are ticking all the boxes here, aren't we?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "You don't?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "It's possible.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Are you going to get divorced, do you think?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Just a lot of things that have happened in our marriage over the years.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Why has it come to this, do you think?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "He has been a bad boy, here and there, over the years.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "A bad boy?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Let's bring in the gurus.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I don't think there should be any secrets.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Do you want to share the rest of your life with him?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Bryce and Brent, right?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Very difficult.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "When you have kids -- you've got three kids -- how much more difficult is it to simply say this marriage is over, move on, when there are kids involved?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Yeah, it would.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Doesn't it eventually erode trust?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "She should follow her heart.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "From what you've heard, what should she do?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Because every guy that you go out with, you're thinking would he be a good step dad?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "That's who I am, you know?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "It's cool, but I know you don't -- I don't know if you watch our show.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Are you dating?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "It depends.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "If you are being self-critical, how much has been your fault and how much has been the guy's fault?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I think it has something to do with where they are in their life curve, frankly.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "Or is it great sex?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Is he right?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Isn't passion key here, ladies?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "I guess because I'm committed to the marriage.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Why are you happily married, do you think?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "I think that's so brilliant, because you have a great business strategy about your marriage.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "What do you think now when you hear that?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "Yes, I think I would.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Well, I have a question.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "How can we help you?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "Now I think he's right.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 799, "question": "What's your view, Lauren?", "qSentId": 798}, {"answer": "It's interesting.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "I was wondering what are your top tips for keeping your partner happy in a relationship?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "I didn't say all the time try -- he should.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "Why don't he try something new?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "Love guru doesn't have an answer to that one.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "Is it going to grow?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "Hi, everyone.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "What's your question?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "Oh, I love that question.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "I want to know she like better, Piers or Anderson Cooper?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "I love Anderson.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "Let's get that one out of the way first?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 866}, {"answer": "I'm not quite sure, but it will be something sexy and romantic with my husband.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "Do you know what you're doing tonight?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "I'm not dating anybody, so I'll just be with myself.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Where will you be tonight?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "Footloose and fancy free in New York?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "I'm free as a bird.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "Mimi, what are you doing?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "I'm in.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "Donnie, you in?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "I think every woman wants to feel special.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "Why do you have to be romantic on this day?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "So it's important to you?", "qSentId": 897}, {"answer": "All the holidays are a big day to me.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 902, "question": "For all three of you, this is a big day?", "qSentId": 901}, {"answer": "Well, she better walk Wall Street.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 905, "question": "She's in New York, any advice?", "qSentId": 904}, {"answer": "One of you producers asked me the same question.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 909, "question": "Where are you going to be?", "qSentId": 908}, {"answer": "I think they should find you.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "The men should come to you, shouldn't they?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 927, "question": "Could you go out with a poor guy?", "qSentId": 926}, {"answer": "He can't be totally poor, because I don't want to take care.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 933, "question": "Could you go out with a poor guy now?", "qSentId": 932}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 936, "question": "So they have to be wealthy?", "qSentId": 935}, {"answer": "I'm taking you.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 947, "question": "You can take me, Donnie or Anderson Cooper?", "qSentId": 946}, {"answer": "Desert island, rest of your life, me, Anderson Cooper, Donnie Deutsch.", "docId": "110214pmt", "aSentId": 950, "question": "Wait, say that again?", "qSentId": 949}]